Finding Aid for Gerald L. K. Smith Papers 1922-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Chronological files
  - 1954
    - Manney, E. E., Publishing Co. (Box 42)
    - Memos (Box 42)
    - Motion Picture Alliance (Box 42)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - New York trip (Box 42)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 42)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Oxnam, G. Bromley (Box 42)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Robertson, Charles (Box 42)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 42)
    - Segregation (Box 42)
    - Senate bulletins (Box 42)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 42)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 42)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Tanner, O. M. (Box 42)
    - Tenney, Jack B.
      - Correspondence (Box 42)
      - Clippings (Box 42)
    - Tisch, Joseph F. (Box 42)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Washington Letter (Box 42)
    - Wheeler, James M. (Box 42)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
  - 1955
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Advertising (Box 43)
    - American Liberties Union (Box 43)
    - Appeal letters (Box 43)
    - Ba-Bo (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Bo-Bz (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 43)
    - Beaty, John (Box 43)
    - Blackmore, John (Box 43)
      (Canadian M. P.)
    - Blank, Helen (Box 43)
    - Bream, R. E. (Box 43)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 43)
    - Brown, John (Box 43)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Circulars (Box 43)
    - Clark, Max (Box 43)
    - Comparet, Bertrand L. (Box 43)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Davis, Phil W., Jr. (Box 43)
    - Deatherage, George (Box 43)
    - Devin-Adair Co. (Box 43)
    - Dilling, Albert. (Box 43)
      (See also Comparet and St. George files)
    - Dog data (Box 43)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 43)
    - Essig, Edith (Box 43)
    - Expiration circulars (Box 43)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - For the Record - miscellaneous papers (Box 43)
    - Foreign letters (Box 43)
    - Frank, John (Box 43)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Green, B. F. (Box 43)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Justa, Stanley (Box 43)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Kahn, J. Kesner (Box 43)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 43)
    - Levitt, Albert (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 44)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Manney, E. E., Printing Co. (Box 44)
    - Marogon, John (Box 44)
    - Memos (Box 44)
    - Mullins, Eustace (Box 44)
    - Murray, William (Box 44)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - National Emergency Conference (Box 44)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 44)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Protocols of Learned Elders of Zion (Box 44)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Recordings (Box 44)
    - Robertson, Charles F. (Box 44)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 44)
    - San Francisco meeting (Box 44)
    - Senate bulletin (Box 44)
      (printed matter distributed to members of Senate)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 44)
    - Sorenson family (Box 44)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 44)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Tanner, O. M. (Box 44)
    - Tenney, Jack (Box 44)
    - Threats (Box 44)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - U. S. Post Office (Box 44)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Washington Letter (Box 44)
    - Washington Letter (Box 44)
      (European Letter)
    - We the People (Box 44)
    - Wheeler, James (Box 44)
    - Wide World (Box 44)
    - Wilkinson Publishing Co. (Box 44)
    - Worrell, Margaret Hopkins (Box 44)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
    - Z (miscellaneous) (Box 44)
  - 1956
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Appeal letters (Box 45)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Beaty, John (Box 45)
    - Blank, Helen (Box 45)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 45)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Circulars (Box 45)
    - Comparet, Bertrand (Box 45)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Deatherage, George (Box 45)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 45)
    - Expirations (Box 45)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Fluoridation (Box 45)
    - For America Committee (Box 45)
    - Foreign letters (Box 45)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Heal, Barbara (Box 45)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Kamp, Joe (Box 45)
    - Kesner-Kahn, Jack (Box 45)
    - Knowland for President ... If Committee (Box 45)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Large Giver Letter (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 45)
    - Lundberg, Dan, Television Show (Box 45)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 45)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 45)
    - Manney Printing Company (Box 45)
    - Manuscripts (Box 46)
    - Memos (Box 46)
    - Miller, Manuel and Lucille (Box 46)
    - Moore, Doris A. (Box 46)
    - Morgan, Roland and Edith (Box 46)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Nearhoofs, Nan and Dona (Box 46)
    - New Letter (Box 46)
    - New York and Florida Mailings (Box 46)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 46)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Press Releases (Box 46)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Republican National Convention, San Francisco (Box 46)
    - Robertson, Charles (Box 46)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Selkirk, Martha S. (Box 46)
    - Senate Bulletins (Box 46)
    - Smith, Gerald L. K. - personal (Box 46)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 46)
    - Sorenson family (Box 46)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 46)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - United Nations (Box 46)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Weinberg, Sidney J. (Box 46)
    - White, Opal and Walter (Box 46)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
  - 1957
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Appeal Letters (Box 46)
    - Arkansas (Box 46)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 46)
    - Beaty, John (Box 46)
    - Blank, Mrs. Helen (Box 46)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Christian National Party (Box 47)
    - Citizens Councils (Box 47)
    - Common Sense (Box 47)
    - Comparet, Bertrand L. (Box 47)
    - Congressional List (Box 47)
    - Constitution Party of California (Box 47)
    - Crommelin, Admiral John (Box 47)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Dallas meetings (Box 47)
    - Devin-Adair Co. (Box 47)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Ellender, Senator Allen J. (Box 47)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 47)
    - Essig, Mrs. Edith R. (Box 47)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Foreign letters (Box 47)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Gaston, Fannie A. (Box 47)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Help Wanted (Box 47)
    - Hollywood High meeting March 28, 1957 (Box 47)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Kesner-Kahn, Jack (Box 47)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - Literature Orders (Box 47)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 47)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 47)
    - Manney, E. E. (Box 47)
    - Manuscripts (Box 47)
    - Martin, Rose (Box 47)
    - Memos (Box 47)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 48)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - San Francisco (Box 48)
    - Senate Bulletins (Box 48)
    - Special Letters for Large Givers (Box 48)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 48)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - United States Post Office (Box 48)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - White, Opal (Box 48)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Z (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
  - 1958
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Appeal letters (Box 48)
    - Appeal (Box 48)
      (responses to special delivery appeals)
    - Arkansas (Box 48)
    - Atlanta (Box 48)
      (bombing of synagogue)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 48)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Comparet, Bertrand L. (Box 48)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Devin-Adair Co. (Box 48)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 48)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 48)
    - Expiration letters (Box 48)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - Fluoridation (Box 49)
    - Foreign letters (Box 49)
    - Frank, John (Box 49)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - "Hate" groups, clippings about (Box 49)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 49)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - Manney Printing Co. (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts (Box 49)
    - Maragon, John (Box 49)
    - Martin, Rose (Box 49)
    - Memos (Box 49)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - New Letter (Box 49)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 49)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 49)
    - San Francisco meeting (Box 49)
    - Smith, Gerald L. K., personal (Box 49)
    - Sorenson family (Box 49)
    - Stephenson, Bill (Box 49)
      (ed., The Virginian)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 49)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - Wills (Box 49)
    - X (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 49)
  - 1959
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Appeal Letters (Box 50)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 50)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Christian National Conference (Box 50)
    - Circulars (Box 50)
    - Comparet (Box 50)
    - Cross and Flag (Box 50)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Devin-Adair (Box 50)
    - Duggan, Tom (Box 50)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Embassy Auditorium (Box 50)
    - Essig, Edith (Box 50)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Falks, Warren H. (Box 50)
    - Foreign letters (Box 50)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Insurance (Box 50)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita (Box 50)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 50)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 51)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Manney Printing Co. (Box 51)
    - Memos (Box 51)
    - Money (Box 51)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Negro (Box 51)
    - New Letters (Box 51)
    - Newspapers (Box 51)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Perkins (Box 51)
    - Petitions (Box 51)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Smith-personal (Box 51)
    - Sorenson family (Box 51)
    - Stratton, Phil (Box 51)
    - Supreme Court (Box 51)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - White, Opal (Box 51)
    - X, Y, Z (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
  - 1960
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Appeal letters (Box 51)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 51)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 51)
    - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 51)
    - Circulars (Box 51)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - Eichmann, Adolph (Box 52)
    - Election fraud (Box 52)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 52)
    - Expirations (Box 52)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - Faubus for President
      - Correspondence (Box 52)
      - Clippings (Box 52)
    - Fluoridation (Box 52)
    - For the Record (Box 52)
    - Foreign letters (Box 52)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - Hart, Merwin K. (Box 52)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 52)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - Memos (Box 52)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 52)
    - New Letter (Box 52)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 52)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Rockwell, George Lincoln (Box 53)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Stratton, Phil (Box 53)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Threats (Box 53)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Welch, Robert (Box 53)
    - White, Opal T. (Box 53)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
  - 1961
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Appeal letters (Box 53)
    - Apple Valley (Box 53)
      (showing of film "Operation Abolition")
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
      (include William Buckley)
    - Beaty, John (Box 53)
    - Birch, John Society (Box 53)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 53)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Christian Nationalist Crusade conference (Box 53)
    - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 53)
    - Cross and the Flag index (Box 53)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 53)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 53)
    - Employees (Box 53)
    - Essig, Edith (Box 53)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Foreign letters (Box 54)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Howard and McDaniel attorneys (Box 54)
      (Time Magazine law suit)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Libel (Box 54)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 54)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Manney Printing Company (Box 54)
    - Memos (Box 54)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
      (include Gamal Nasser)
    - New Letter (Box 54)
    - Norfleet, Marvin Brooks (Box 54)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Robertson, Charles B. (Box 54)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - W-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 54)
    - Weston, Pat (Box 54)
    - Winegarner, Charles (Box 54)
  - 1962
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Anti-Defamation League (Box 55)
    - Antiques (Box 55)
    - Appeal letters (Box 55)
    - Arrowsmith, Harold (Box 55)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 55)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 55)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 55)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Foreign letters (Box 55)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 55)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 55)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Manney Publishing Company (Box 55)
    - Manuscripts - published essays (Box 56)
    - Memos (Box 56)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - New Letter (Box 56)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 56)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Paddock, Frances estate (Box 56)
    - Pike, James (Box 56)
    - "Right-wing" organizations and publications (Box 56)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - San Francisco meeting (Box 56)
    - Schwarz, Fred (Box 56)
      (Christian Anti-Communist Crusade)
    - Southern Michigan University (Box 56)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Time Magazine (libel suit) (Box 56)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
      (include Robert Welch)
    - Walker, Edwin (Box 56)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
  - 1963
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Anti-Defamation League (Box 56)
    - App, Austin (Box 56)
    - Appeal letters (Box 56)
    - Apple Valley (Box 56)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Brooks, Austen (Box 57)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 57)
    - Citizens Congressional Committee (Box 57)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Defense Act (Box 57)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 57)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Foreign letters (Box 57)
    - Fields, Edward R. (Box 57)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Grant, A. V. (Box 57)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Kennedy, John F (about) (Box 57)
    - Kuchel, Thomas (Box 57)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 57)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Memos (Box 57)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - New Letter (Box 57)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
      (include George Lincoln Rockwell)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Tracy, Dick (Box 58)
      (pseud. of polemicist)
    - "Treason Treaty" (Box 58)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
  - 1964
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Antiques (Box 58)
    - Appeal letters (Box 58)
    - Apple Valley (Box 58)
    - Archives document (Box 58)
      (original photostat)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Becker, Frank J. (Box 58)
      (congressman)
    - Bonus checks (Box 58)
    - Butler, Eric (Box 58)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Driftwood, Charlie (Box 58)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 58)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Foreign letters (Box 58)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - M (Box 59)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (Box 59)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 59)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Pamphlets filed in CYAC office (Box 59)
    - Pegler, Westbrook (Box 59)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Rentals (Box 59)
    - Salton Sea (Box 59)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - W-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Wallace, George (Box 59)
  - 1965
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Acknowledgment letters (Box 59)
    - Appeal letters (Box 59)
    - Appeals (Box 59)
      (personal visits with GLKS)
    - Apple Valley (Box 59)
    - Ba-Bo (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Bp-Bz (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Big Bear Lake (Box 59)
    - Bishops (Box 59)
    - Ca-Cm (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Co-Cz (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 59)
    - Circulars (Box 59)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 60)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Foreign letters (Box 60)
    - Form letters (Box 60)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Goldwater mailings (Box 60)
    - Ha-He (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Hi-Hz (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Large donor letters (Box 60)
    - Ma-Mi (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Mo-Mz (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Maines, George (Box 60)
    - Meeting circulars (Box 60)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
      (include Westbrook Pegler)
    - Ra-Rn (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Ro-Rz (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Sa-Sl (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Sm-Sz (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Statue, Eureka Springs - clippings (Box 61)
    - Stock gift (Box 61)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Wa-Wh (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Wi-Wz (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - X-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
  - 1966 (fragmentary)
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Appeal letters (Box 61)
    - Arab (Box 61)
    - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 61)
    - Citizens Congressional Committee (Box 61)
    - Delay letters (Box 61)
    - Embassy Auditorium contracts (Box 61)
    - For the Record (Box 61)
    - Literature List (Box 61)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Memoirs (Box 61)
      (also include earlier collected clippings and correspondence)
    - Publications (Box 61)
    - Salton Sea (Box 61)
    - Smith, E. M., Foundation (Box 61)
    - Statue, Eureka Springs (Box 61)
    - Volume notices (Box 61)
    - Will (Box 61)
    - Wolf House (Box 61)
  - 1967 (fragmentary)
    - Big Bear Lake (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 61)
    - University of Michigan (Box 61)
  - 1968
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - B-M (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Large donors" (Box 62)
    - N-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
  - 1969
    - A-C (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - D-N (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Newspaper clippings" (Box 64)
    - O-Z (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Staff" (Box 65)
  - 1970
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - B-F (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Capell, Frank A." (Box 66)
    - G-M (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - N-W (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Newspaper clippings", and "Robertson, Charles F." (Box 68)
    - W-Z (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "White, Opal Tanner" (Box 69)
  - 1971
    - A-G (miscellaneous) (Box 69)
    - G-O (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Newspaper clippings" (Box 70)
    - P-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 71)
  - 1972
    - A-B (miscellaneous) (Box 71)
    - B-H (miscellaneous) (Box 72)
    - I-S (miscellaneous); include individual file folder for "Newspaper clippings" (Box 73)
    - T-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 74)
  - 1973
    - A-F (miscellaneous) (Box 74)
    - G-Q (miscellaneous) (Box 75)
    - R-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 76)
  - 1974
    - A-B (miscellaneous) (Box 76)
    - C-K (miscellaneous) (Box 77)
    - L-S (miscellaneous) (Box 78)
    - T-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 79)
  - 1975
    - A-E (miscellaneous) (Box 79)
    - F-P (miscellaneous) (Box 80)
    - R-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 81)
  - 1977
    - Cross and the Flag statement of mailing-2nd class publications (Box 81)
- Personal (scattered dates)
  The small Personal series include such items as an account book, Christmas card lists, income tax material, and membership cards.
  - Account book 1942-1945 (Box 81)
  - Automobile purchases (Box 81)
  - Christmas card lists, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Income tax miscellanea (Box 81)
  - Insurance materials (Box 81)
  - Manuscript: "The Red Orchestra" (Box 81)
  - Membership and business cards (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 81)
  - Smith, Gerry - schooling records (Box 81)
- Administrative files